Vivienne Malone-Mayes papers, Inclusive: 1966-1977, undated; Bulk: 1973-1976
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Mental Health Mental Retardation Center, 1967-1977, undated; 1
  - 1975, 4
    - Budget: Annual: City of Waco (6 of 10), 1975 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Budget: Annual: City of Waco (7 of 10), 1975 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Budget: Annual: City of Waco (8 of 10), 1975 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Budget: Annual: City of Waco (9 of 10), 1975 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Budget: Annual: City of Waco (10 of 10), 1975 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: General, 1975 January-March (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: General, 1975 March-May 7 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: General, 1975 May 15-June (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: General, 1975 July (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: General, 1975 October (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: General, 1975 November-December (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1975 January (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1975 February-March (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1975 March-May 7 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1975 May 15 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1975 June-August (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1975 September (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1975 October (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1975 December (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Executive Director, 1975 February 11-13 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Executive Director, 1975 February 20-March 11 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Executive Director, 1975 March 17 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Personnel Services (1 of 2), 1975 May 12 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Personnel Services (2 of 2), 1975 May 12 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Personnel Services, 1975 May 14-15 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Personnel Services (1 of 2), 1975 May 15 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Personnel Services (2 of 2), 1975 May 15 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Personnel Services, 1975 May 16-27 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Personnel Services, 1975 June (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Search Committee, 1975 April-June 19 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Search Committee, 1975 June 23-30 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Vivienne Malone-Mayes, 1975 July-November (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Financial Documents: General, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Legal Documents: General, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Manual: Personnel Policies (1 of 3), circa 1975 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Manual: Personnel Policies (2 of 3), circa 1975 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Manual: Personnel Policies (3 of 3), circa 1975 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Manual: Rules, Regulations, and Standards, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1975 January (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1975 February-August (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1975 September-December 10 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1975 December 17 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Minutes: Planning Session, 1975 October 2 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Packet: Teaching Chief for Psychiatry Position: Bernard Spector, 1975 April-May (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Periodicals: Impact, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Report: 1976 Budget, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Report: Annual: Harris County Center for the Retarded, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Report: Community Programs Patient Information System: Fiscal Year, 1975 November 19 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Report: Community Programs Patient Information System: Fiscal Year, 1975 December 2 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Report: Community Programs Patient Information System: Fourth Quarter (1 of 2), 1975 November 15 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Report: Community Programs Patient Information System: Fourth Quarter (2 of 2), 1975 November 15 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Report: Examination, 1975 August 31 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Report: “Explanation of Grant Application” (1 of 2), 1975 March 26 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Report: “Explanation of Grant Application” (2 of 2), 1975 March 26 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Report: “Guidelines for Annual Fiscal Audits of Community MHMR Centers”, 1975 June (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (1 of 2), 1975 January (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (2 of 2), 1975 January (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (1 of 2), 1975 February (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (2 of 2), 1975 February (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (1 of 2), 1975 March (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (2 of 2), 1975 March (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (1 of 2), 1975 April (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (2 of 2), 1975 April (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (1 of 2), 1975 May (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (2 of 2), 1975 May (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (1 of 2), 1975 July (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (2 of 2), 1975 July (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure, 1975 December (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Report: Transmittal Form for Budgets, 1975 January 6 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Report: Transmittal Form for Budgets (1 of 4), 1975 August 12 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Report: Transmittal Form for Budgets (2 of 4), 1975 August 12 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Report: Transmittal Form for Budgets (3 of 4), 1975 August 12 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Report: Transmittal Form for Budgets (4 of 4), 1975 August 12 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Reports: General, 1975 January-June (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Reports: General, 1975 August-October (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Schedule: Interview: Dr. Bernard Spector, 1975 February 19-23 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Statistics: General, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - 1976, 1975-1976; 5
    The following subseries contains materials produced by the Heart of Texas Region Mental Health and Mental Retardation Center in 1976. These include correspondence, minutes, and financial reports.
    - Agenda: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (1 of 5), 1976 August 20 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Agenda: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (2 of 5), 1976 August 20 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Agenda: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (3 of 5), 1976 August 20 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Agenda: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (4 of 5), 1976 August 20 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Agenda: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (5 of 5), 1976 August 20 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Agenda: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (1 of 5), 1976 October 22 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Agenda: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (2 of 5), 1976 October 22 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Agenda: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (3 of 5), 1976 October 22 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Agenda: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (4 of 5), 1976 October 22 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Agenda: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (5 of 5), 1976 October 22 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Agenda: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (1 of 4), 1976 December 17 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Agenda: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (2 of 4), 1976 December 17 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Agenda: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (3 of 4), 1976 December 17 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Agenda: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (4 of 4), 1976 December 17 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Application: Construction Grant (1 of 5), 1976 April (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Application: Construction Grant (2 of 5), 1976 April (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Application: Construction Grant (3 of 5), 1976 April (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Application: Construction Grant (4 of 5), 1976 April (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Application: Construction Grant (5 of 5), 1976 April (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Booklet: Money for Mental Health, circa 1976 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - By-Laws: Texas Council of Community Mental Health Mental Retardation Centers, circa 1976 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Contract: Professional Liability Insurance Policy, 1976 November (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: General, 1976 February-March (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: General, 1976 April-June 14 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: General, 1976 June 24-August 26 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: General, 1976 August 28-December (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1976 February (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1976 March (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1976 April (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1976 May (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1976 June (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1976 July (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1976 August (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1976 October (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Directories: Board Chairmen: Mental Health and Mental Retardation Centers, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Financial Documents: General, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Legal Documents: General, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Manual: Personnel Policies and Procedures, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Manual: Personnel Policies and Procedures (1 of 3), 1976 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Manual: Personnel Policies and Procedures (2 of 3), 1976 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Manual: Personnel Policies and Procedures (3 of 3), 1976 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1976 January (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1976 February-April (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1976 May (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1976 June-September (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1976 October (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Minutes: Board of Trustees, 1976 November-December (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Minutes: Planning Committee, 1976 March (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Minutes: Planning Committee, 1976 April (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (1 of 4), 1976 April 23 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (2 of 4), 1976 April 23 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (3 of 4), 1976 April 23 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (4 of 4), 1976 April 23 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (1 of 3), 1976 July 9 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (2 of 3), 1976 July 9 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (3 of 3), 1976 July 9 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (1 of 6), 1976 August 20 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (2 of 6), 1976 August 20 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (3 of 6), 1976 August 20 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (4 of 6), 1976 August 20 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (5 of 6), 1976 August 20 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (6 of 6), 1976 August 20 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (1 of 4), 1976 October 22 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (2 of 4), 1976 October 22 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (3 of 4), 1976 October 22 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (4 of 4), 1976 October 22 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Minutes: Texas State Advisory Council for Construction of Community Mental Health Centers, 1976 May 3-4 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Packet: Board Meeting for January 1976, 1975 December (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Packet: Board Meeting for January 1976, 1976 January 1-14 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Packet: Board Meeting for January 1976, 1976 January 16-28 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Packet: Board Meeting for February 1976, 1976 February (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Packet: “Budget Request for State Grant-in-Aid for Community MHMR Centers, Fiscal Years 1978 and 1979” (1 of 2), 1976 October (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Packet: “Budget Request for State Grant-in-Aid for Community MHMR Centers, Fiscal Years 1978 and 1979” (2 of 2), 1976 October (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Packet: Distribution of State Grant-in-Aid for 1977 Fiscal Year (1 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Packet: Distribution of State Grant-in-Aid for 1977 Fiscal Year (2 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Packet: Topics for Board Meeting, circa 1976 October (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Pamphlet: “Rules of the Commissioner”, 1976 January (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Periodical: Impact, 1976 September (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Printed Materials: General, 1976 January-June (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Printed Materials: General, 1976 August-December (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Printed Materials: General, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Report: “An Addendum to the 1973-74 Texas State Plan for Construction of Community Mental Health Centers for Fiscal Year 1975” (1 of 6), 1976 April (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Report: “An Addendum to the 1973-74 Texas State Plan for Construction of Community Mental Health Centers for Fiscal Year 1975” (2 of 6), 1976 April (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Report: “An Addendum to the 1973-74 Texas State Plan for Construction of Community Mental Health Centers for Fiscal Year 1975” (3 of 6), 1976 April (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Report: “An Addendum to the 1973-74 Texas State Plan for Construction of Community Mental Health Centers for Fiscal Year 1975” (4 of 6), 1976 April (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Report: “An Addendum to the 1973-74 Texas State Plan for Construction of Community Mental Health Centers for Fiscal Year 1975” (5 of 6), 1976 April (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Report: “An Addendum to the 1973-74 Texas State Plan for Construction of Community Mental Health Centers for Fiscal Year 1975” (6 of 6), 1976 April (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Report: Annual: Health Coordinating Board, 1976 June 7 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Report: Client Service Statistics (1 of 2), 1976 April (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Report: Client Service Statistics (2 of 2), 1976 April (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Report: Community Center Personal Schedule, 1976 April 22 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Report: Community Services Division: Site Visit, 1976 January 26-28 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Report: Examination, 1976 August 31 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure, 1976 January (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure, 1976 February (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure, 1976 March 31 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure, 1976 May 31 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (1 of 2), 1976 June 30 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (2 of 2), 1976 June 30 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (1 of 8), 1976 August (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (2 of 8), 1976 August (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (3 of 8), 1976 August (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (4 of 8), 1976 August (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (5 of 8), 1976 August (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (6 of 8), 1976 August (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (7 of 8), 1976 August (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure (8 of 8), 1976 August (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Report: Revenue and Expenditure, 1976 December 31 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Report: Revised Budget for 1976 Fiscal Year (1 of 3) (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Report: Revised Budget for 1976 Fiscal Year (2 of 3) (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Report: Revised Budget for 1976 Fiscal Year (3 of 3) (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Report: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation: Budget Requests for 1978-1979 Biennium (1 of 2), 1976 February (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Report: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation: Budget Requests for 1978-1979 Biennium (2 of 2), 1976 February (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Reports: Monthly Services, 1976 November-December (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Speech: Mary Teague: “Roles and Responsibilities of Board Members”, 1976 August 28 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Statistics: General, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - 1977, 6
    This subseries contains materials produced by the Heart of Texas Region Mental Health Mental Retardation Center in 1977 including correspondence, financial documents, and minutes from the Board of Trustees.
    The materials in this subseries are organized alphabetically according to type of material.
    - Correspondence: Board of Trustees, 1977 January-February (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Financial Documents: General, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Manual: Board of Trustees (1 of 10), 1977 May (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Manual: Board of Trustees (2 of 10), 1977 May (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Manual: Board of Trustees (3 of 10), 1977 May (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Manual: Board of Trustees (4 of 10), 1977 May (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Manual: Board of Trustees (5 of 10), 1977 May (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Manual: Board of Trustees (6 of 10), 1977 May (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Manual: Board of Trustees (7 of 10), 1977 May (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Manual: Board of Trustees (8 of 10), 1977 May (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Manual: Board of Trustees (9 of 10), 1977 May (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Manual: Board of Trustees (10 of 10), 1977 May (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (1 of 6), 1977 January (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (2 of 6), 1977 January (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (3 of 6), 1977 January (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (4 of 6), 1977 January (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (5 of 6), 1977 January (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (6 of 6), 1977 January (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (1 of 4), 1977 February (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (2 of 4), 1977 February (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (3 of 4), 1977 February (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Minutes: Texas Board of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (4 of 4), 1977 February (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Report: “Executive Budget, 1978-1979 Biennium”, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Undated, 7
    This subseries contains all the materials produced from the Heart of Texas Mental Health Mental Retardation Center that did not have a definitive date assigned to them.
    - Essay: “Historical Sketch of the Providence Hospital Community Health Center and Its Relationship to the Waco-McLennan County Mental Health and Mental Retardation Board”, undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Guidelines: Job Descriptions, undated (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Guidelines: “Rules Governing the Waco-McLennan County Mental Health Mental Retardation Center”, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Manual: Organizational Operations, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Printed Materials: General (1 of 2), undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Printed Materials: General (2 of 2), undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Review: Mental Retardation Program, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Surveys: Mental Health (1 of 2), undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Surveys: Mental Health (2 of 2), undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Baylor Mathematics Department, 1975-1977, undated; 2
  This series contains coursework, quizzes, notes, correspondence, and other materials collected by Dr. Vivienne Malone-Mayes during her early years as a Professor of Mathematics at Baylor University.
  The materials within this series are organized according to type.
  - Correspondence: General, 1975-1977, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Secondary School Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Coursework: General, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Coursework: Math 107 (1 of 4), undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Coursework: Math 107 (2 of 4), undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Coursework: Math 107 (3 of 4), undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Coursework: Math 107 (4 of 4), undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Dissertation: Matthew Liu (1 of 4), 1975 May (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Dissertation: Matthew Liu (2 of 4), 1975 May (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Dissertation: Matthew Liu (3 of 4), 1975 May (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Dissertation: Matthew Liu (4 of 4), 1975 May (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Literary Productions: General, 1976-1977, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Notes: Set Theory, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Personal Materials, 1966-1977, undated; 3
  This series contains a few personal materials belonging to Dr. Malone-Mayes including correspondence, radio reports, programs, and other literary productions. The materials are in excellent condition.
  The materials within this series are organized according to type of material.
  - Clippings: Plays, 1970-1973, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: General, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Photograph: General, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Programs: Plays, 1966-1974 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Reports: Public Communication Foundation for North Texas, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Reports: Public Communication Foundation for North Texas, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 12)